[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CALOY] 'Bi?
[BEA] I'll wait for you outside.
[SHARP STAB]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [COP GROANING]
[CALOY] I knew you couldn't
stay away from me.
We have a lot of work to do.
- [JUDE] Cake. Cake.
- [BILLY] Just one slice.
You again?!
I told you not to come back!
Calm down. It's not him.
[JORDAN]
This was supposed to be just for you.
[BILLY] Ever since we were kids, we've
always celebrated our birthdays together.
So it can't be just about me!
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
To me!
- [JORDAN] This is your birthday gift.
- Wow! You're so sweet.
Open it.
No way.
[JORDAN SINGING]
♪ When you come home ♪
♪ Weighed down and broken ♪
♪ I can tell ♪
♪ By the words unspoken ♪
♪ So come here by my side ♪
♪ Let's leave the rest
Of the world aside ♪
♪ Just lean on me ♪
[ENRICO] I'll never get tired of asking
for your forgiveness, Billy.
I understand why you can't
forgive me right away.
I should've been the one
you could lean on.
But I wasn't there for you.
Either of you.
I just hope you'll give me another chance.
Happy birthday, my Billy.
I'm very proud of you.
♪ Just lean on me ♪
♪ Let's leave the rest
Of the world aside ♪
♪ With all its baggage ♪
♪ Whatever happens ♪
♪ Lean on me ♪
♪ Just lean on me ♪
- [CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
- Okay.
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
- Thank you.
- [FRIENDS] That was great!
[APPLAUDING]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- [ENGINE CRANKS]
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- [CLEARS THROAT]
What?
- Yes?
- Billy.
Can you even drive right now?
Of course!
- I'm fine. Mm-mm.
- [JORDAN] You sure?
Yeah, absolutely.
- Thanks for your concern.
- Okay.
[BILLY] And thanks
for performing that song earlier.
- Of course.
- It was beautiful.
- [SINGING] ♪ Lean on me ♪
- [SEATBELT CLICKS]
- ♪ Just lean on me ♪
- ♪ Lean on me ♪
[BOTH SINGING]
♪ Lean on me ♪
♪ Just lean on me ♪
- It was beautiful.
- You know, let's duet sometime.
No way!
You can make me your partner
in everything else, just not in singing.
- Okay?
- Please?
No!
- Okay?
- Dude, come on!
Ugh! I have to go, Jordan.
- [JORDAN CHUCKLES]
- Happy birthday!
- Happy birthday too.
- You're the best! Goodbye!
- Take care.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Everything's all set.
I'm ready.
I'm on my way to Billy's.
Caloy…
Be careful, okay?
Especially since you're still wanted.
[BEA] There are cops
right outside the house.
They're keeping watch.
Probably because they believe
we're connected.
Don't worry.
You won't get dragged into this.
I'll make it up to you, okay?
I love you.
Um…
Love you too.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROBBIE] You're seriously amazing, boss!
That song was so good. Listen--
[SINGING]
♪ Lay your head on me ♪
♪ Just lay your head-- ♪
♪ Lean on me ♪
Oh, were the lyrics "Lean on me"?
- [CHUCKLES] You're wrong!
- Sorry.
♪ Lean on me ♪
♪ Just lean on me ♪
- [RAIN] There you go.
- [LAUGHS]
But seriously…
Is that really a friendship song?
Because to me, it sounds like a love song.
That's just you.
Then what about Billy?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY] Billy's my friend.
Hmm?
It's a friendship song.
Seems more like a love song to me.
It literally says "lean on me."
Would I tell a friend to lean on me?
- No.
- That's just your perspective.
Because all you ever think about is love.
You know, Robbie still has his hopes up
because Valerie has just
broken up with Kevin.
I don't get him.
Good luck to you.
Whatever.
But it's a love song, right?
- He already said it's a friendship song.
- [ROBBIE] It's a love song!
Then tell me, how did it become
a friendship song?
Go, explain it to me. You can't, can you?
It's a love song.
It's friendship. I listened to the lyrics.
- I also listened to them!
- It's about friends.
It's also about the person
you want to lean on you.
It could be both.
[JORDAN] It depends on the listener.
But personally, I wrote it for a friend.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey. Is this true?
[JORDAN] What is it?
Caloy escaped!
What?!
[FOREBODING MUSIC BUILDS,
THEN SLOWLY FADES]
[WATER TRICKLING]
- Hey, Billy!
- [BILLY YELPS]
Did you see it?
- I didn't even take it out!
- No, I didn't see anything.
[PRECIOUS] Why did you
even get thirsty at this time?
Yeah, why did I even get thirsty?
It was supposed to be a surprise.
Was it a surprise?
I didn't expect it, Auntie Pres!
Although you've been doing it
for 15 years every year.
Still, it should've been a surprise.
Thank you.
Happy birthday.
[BILLY] Hm.
[GASPS] I'm so surprised!
- Thank you!
- You're welcome.
But for tomorrow…
- Pretend that this is the cake.
- [BILLY GASPS]
Do you want to eat it already?
- Not yet.
- Okay, we'll eat it tomorrow.
- I won't remember this.
- You saw nothing, right?
I didn't see anything!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGING]
C'mon, dude. C'mon!
[LINE CONTINUES RINGING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC FADING]
Good night.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
- [STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SPRAY PAINT HISSING]
- [BILLY GRUNTS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Hurry up. Hurry up.
[GRUNTS]
- Give up already!
- [YELLS] Help! Let me go!
- [GRUNTING, GROANING]
- Stop resisting!
- Auntie Pres! Help!
- Stop it!
Shut up-- [CALOY YELPS]
- [BILLY YELPS]
- [HEAVY THUD]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Auntie, was that Billy?
Stay there and lock the door.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
My God, Billy!
Billy!
Billy?
Help! Please help us!
Billy? Billy!
My God, Billy, what happened?
Billy! Billy. Billy?
Help!
Please help us!
Billy? Billy, Billy, Billy.
My God!
Jordan!
Jordan, help me!
- Auntie Pres!
- Billy?
- What happened to Billy?
- Watch her for a second.
I'll call an ambulance.
Dude!
[JORDAN] Billy.
Hey.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Why did you punch him?
You should've let it go.
They were teasing me.
They said I'd fail to get
into computer engineering.
Once your mother finds out about this,
she will be furious again.
Well, I have a peace offering.
Wow, you even have a bribe.
[LAUGHING]
Look at this kid.
[CHUCKLES]
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
Jade?
Jade!
[YOUNG JORDAN] Mommy!
Mommy!
[CRYING] Mommy!
[SNIFFLES] Mommy…
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLES] Come on, please.
[JORDAN] Billy?
Billy!
Dude…
Hey.
I'm here.
Stay with me, okay?
Please.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
- Billy?
- Dude.
How do you feel?
I'm okay.
I already spoke to the doctor.
They said they didn't find any bleeding
or fractures on your scan.
You'll be okay.
What about Oliver?
And Auntie Pres? Where are they?
They're safe.
They just went to get some food.
Don't worry.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Did they catch Caloy?
Was he the one who did this?
[MUSIC BECOMES PENSIVE]
I caught him.
He'd already gotten to our house.
- [SPRAY PAINT HISSING]
- [BILLY GRUNTS]
Hurry up.
- Stop resisting!
- Help! Let me go! [GRUNTS]
[THUDS]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey.
I heard
he escaped from the hospital.
I went straight to your house,
but when I got there,
you were already unconscious.
Dude, you scared the shit out of me.
Sorry.
When are they going to stop?
What they're doing to us
just keeps getting worse.
Right now,
what matters is you're okay.
What if…?
I just don't know what I'd do if…
I'm just glad you're okay.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- Hey.
- Billy!
Hi.
- Hey.
- [OLIVER CRYING]
- How are you?
- Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
- Don't leave me.
- No, I'm okay now.
- Promise?
- Mm-hmm.
Sorry I made you worry.
[OLIVER CRYING]
[BILLY] It's okay now.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
She fought back, so I beat her up.
I slammed her head against the wall.
For heaven's sake, Caloy!
What is wrong with you?!
Every single one of your plans fails!
You messed up again!
Well, she thought she could outsmart me.
My instructions were crystal clear.
Weren't they?
Why did you hurt her?
You were just supposed to spray-paint
their walls to scare her! That's it!
Why did you hurt her?
He hurt Billy?
Serves her right!
- [CALL DISCONNECTS]
- Hello?
[BEEPING]
Come on, 'Bi…
You were detained.
You lost your job.
You've got a case against you.
And all of that happened because of Billy.
If she wants to make sure
you end up in prison,
I'm not letting that happen.
Ma, I don't want to go to prison either.
Who would?
But Caloy keeps screwing things up.
Think about it, Ma.
If one of us gets caught,
we'll all get dragged into this.
Well, if you don't want to do it,
Caloy and I will do it for you.
Hey, Ma.
Stay out of this.
I've already got it handled.
You don't need to get involved.
She's already ruined
every plan you had for us.
That's why what Caloy did
was the right thing.
What's gotten into you?
Are you sick?
You're not angry at Caloy anymore?
Not as long as he doesn't take you
away from me.
That really won't happen.
That will never happen.
But you know,
even though Caloy messed up,
maybe it'll still work.
Maybe it'll scare Billy enough
for her to finally leave me alone.
I hope so.
When you were detained,
I was all alone in this house.
It reminded me of when your sister died.
It hurt so much.
Being left behind hurts so much.
That's why I promised myself
I'd never go through that again.
Never.
Especially not with you.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll never leave you, Ma.
- [NEIGHBOR 1] Come on.
- [NEIGHBOR 2] Let's check.
- [NEIGHBOR 1] Let's hurry.
- [NEIGHBOR 2] My goodness.
- [NEIGHBOR 1] How scary.
- [NEIGHBOR 2] My gosh.
[NEIGHBOR 1] Apparently, someone broke in,
and Billy fought back.
[NEIGHBOR 2] What? Oh my God,
I hope they're okay!
[ENRICO] What happened here?
[NEIGHBOR 1] Someone broke in.
The intruder even spray-painted
their walls.
How are the people who live here?
Where are they?
[NEIGHBOR 2] Billy probably
got hurt fighting back.
They took her to the hospital.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
Billy.
Let the police do their job.
What can you even do right now?
LoveList is finally back on its feet.
Just focus on getting better.
You're not thinking of
getting back at them, are you?
But they've gone too far, Auntie Pres.
But this will never end.
If you retaliate,
they'll just retaliate again.
Think of your brother.
That's exactly why I'm worried, Auntie.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
They were able to break into our house.
What's next?
I need to stop them
before Oliver gets hurt.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Nurse, which room is Benilda Cariño in?
Okay, sir. Hold on.
I'll check which room she's in.
Cariño…
[STIRRING MUSIC SWELLS]
I'm worried whoever broke in
might come back,
so I'm watching him in school.
You really feel more at ease
when your child is with you.
We won't have any peace
until that Billy leaves us alone!
[BEA] Let me deal with Billy.
I'll handle her, okay?
Sir, what's the update on Bea Mercado?
Bea Mercado has been under surveillance
since last week.
That's what you guys always say.
But nothing ever happens.
Why can't you just
leave Oliver to himself?
He's not a baby.
You just don't understand.
Understand what?
- That you're just leading me on?
- It's not like that, Brandon.
[BRANDON] You know,
you just wasted my time.
I just realized how important
she is to me.
- I knew it.
- She's like my family.
I'll tell the truth.
[STIRRING MUSIC SWELLS]